<resources>
    <string name="app_name">mailbot</string>

    <!--Main Activity Strings-->
    <string name="mainActivitySpeech">Hi! My name is MailBot and I am here to deliver your letters or your parcels to anyone in the EEE building!\n\nChoose what type of mail item you want to deliver to start organising your delivery!</string>

    <string name="letterStandardText">Letter\n(Standard size)</string>
    <string name="letterLargeText">Large Letter\n(around A4)</string>
    <string name="parcelText">Parcel\n(up to 00x00cm)</string>

    <string name="lockerSizeUnavailable">All lockers of this size are full</string>

    <!--Details Activity Strings-->
    <string name="infoDetailsActivity">That\'s great! I just need to know a little bit about you...</string>

    <string name="fieldName">Name: </string>
    <string name="fieldEmail">Email Address: </string>
    <string name="userChoosePhoto">Take a photo? </string>

    <string name="bubbleRecipientDetails">Perfect! Now please tell us the details of the recipient of your mail item.</string>

    <string name="emailError">Please give a valid email address</string>
    <string name="emptyNameField">Please enter a name</string>
    <string name="emptyEmailField">Please enter an email address</string>

    <!--Will this need multiple lines?-->
    <string name="recipientLocation">Delivery Location: </string>

    <string name="confirmSpeechBubble">Please confirm to me that the details below are correct.</string>

    <string name="senderDetailsSpinner">Sender Details</string>
    <string name="recipientDetailsSpinner">Recipient Details</string>

    <!--Locker Activity Strings-->
    <string name="lockerActivitySpeech">I have opened locker X for your mail item! Please store it there so I can deliver it, and close the locker before continuing.</string>
    <string name="lockerActivityBadFit">It doesn\'t fit!</string>
    <string name="lockerActivityGoodFit">I put the parcel in and closed the locker!</string>
    <string name="packageTooBig">The mail item is too big to fit in MailBot</string>

    <!--End Activity Strings-->
    <string name="endActivitySpeech">Thank you for giving me your mail! It will be delivered in the next delivery slot time, and a confirmation e-mail with the security code for the recipient to open the locker has been sent to both you and the recipient.
    Use the buttons below to send another mail item to the same recipient, or begin again!</string>
    <string name="toSameRecipient">Same recipient</string>
    <string name="startAgain">Return</string>
    <string name="enRouteActivitySpeech">I am now delivering the mail items that have been handed to me! If you want to send your own mail item, find me in reception at the next collection time!</string>
    <string name="openLockerActivitySpeech">That\'s the correct password! A locker for your mail item has been opened! Please retrieve your item, and then close the locker.</string>
</resources>
